Rohan Jain

github.com/rjain37/ linkedin.com/in/rjain37/ 8920 Royal Drive Burr Ridge, Illinois 60527

rjain.dev rohan@rjain.dev +1 (630)-303-7920

Summary

Rising junior at the Illinois Mathematics and Science Academy interested in an industry position to bolster professional skills. Experienced with web development. 3 years of programming experience, primarily with Java, HTML/CSS/JS, MySQL, and Node.JS. Extensive involvement with Github and Linux as well. Highly reinforced mathematical background, having taken classes in multi-variable calculus, differential equations, statistics and competed in math competitions for 2 years.

Experience

Tutor Sep. 2017 – Present

Math and Programming Tutoring

Burr Ridge, IL

- · Tutoring students to get their grades up
- · Helping young students get involved in competitive math (MATHCOUNTS, Math Kangaroo, AMC, etc.)
- Teaching young students how to code to envelop an interest in computer science

Apr. 2021 - Present **JHMC Assistant**

Annual Junior High Math Competition

Aurora, IL

- · Using JavaScript to create server side scripts
- · Writing hundreds of math problems annually
- · Spreading a love of competition math in middle schoolers

Education

Illinois Mathematics and Science Academy

GPA: 4.0/4.0

Aug. 2020 - Present Aurora, Illinois

Hinsdale South High School

GPA: 6.0/6.0

Aug. 2019 - Jun. 2020 Darien, Illinois

Skills and Tools

Programming Languages: C/C++; HTML/CSS/JS; Java; MySQL; Node.JS; PHP

Technologies: Git/GitHub; LaTeX; Linux; Slurm

Frameworks: Express.JS; React

Languages: English(Native); Korean(Heritage); Spanish(Advanced)

Extracurricular

Open Source: Contributed to IMSA Grades

A website to display the history of grades in all classes at my school

Competitions:

- AMC 10 A 2021 Distinguished Honor Roll (Top 1%) of participants
- AMC 10 B 2021 Distinguished Honor Roll (Top 1%) of participants

Hackthons:

- SASEhack 2020 4th place team
- · Epoch x IMSA GWC participant